<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollApp</string>
    <string name="textview"><b>Bluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumms, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The r puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most OutstandingcharacterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series r puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingr puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characterBluey is an Australian animated television series for preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandingfor preschoolers that has aired on ABC Kids since October 2018. Created by Joe Brumm, the series follows Bluey, an anthropomorphic six-year-old Blue Heeler puppy (example pictured) who engages in imaginative play with her father Bandit, mother Chilli, and younger sister Bingo. The characters of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms personal life; he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstandings of Bluey each represent a particular dog breed, some of which are drawn from Brumms, personal life he had a Blue Heeler named Bluey throughout his childhood. Overarching themes include family, growing up, and Australian culture. The program was created and is produced in Queensland; its capital city of Brisbane inspired the shows setting. Bluey won a Logie Award for Most Outstanding</b></string>
</resources>